<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Scar Removal Drug</name>
  <author>Pikes</author>
  <url></url>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
	<li>1.5</li>
	<li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Pikes.ScarRemovalDrug</packageId>
  <description><![CDATA[<b>A simple mod adding a new drug for healing permanent injuries or chronic conditions ailments after some time.</b>

<b>What is this new drug exactly?</b>

It's called "Fibrocerium" (from fibrosis, cerebrum, and luciferium) and can heal one scar, old wound or one of the chronic condition ailments: Alzheimer's, artery blockage, asthma, bad back, blindness, cataract, carcinoma, dementia, frail and hearing loss in 15 to 30 days.

<b>How to buy or make fibrocerium?</b>

Fibrocerium can be bought from faction bases and exotic goods traders for a market value of 385 silver. The trade value, with the 140% modifier and a colonist's Trade Price Improvement stat at 100%, is <b>540 silver</b>. That's the cost of fibrocerium, <b>when bought</b>, to heal one permanent injury or chronic condition ailment.

Research "Fibrocerium production" (600 research points, behind "Drug production").
A pill of fibrocerium is made with 1 luciferium, 2 glitterworld medicine, and 10 neutroamines at a drug lab production bench with a minimum skilled colonist of 3 in intellectual and crafting.
The market value of those products is 230 silver (70 for luciferium, 100 for glitterworld medicine, and 60 for ten neutroamines), but the trade value, with the 140% modifier and a colonist's Trade Price Improvement stat at 100%, is <b>322 silver</b>. That's the cost of fibrocerium, <b>when produced</b>, to heal one permanent injury or chronic condition ailment.

It's a quick way to heal scar, old wound and chronic conditions ailments. It can be bought at any moment or produced at the start of the industrial tech level, needing only "Drug production" as a prerequisite.

<b>How to use fibrocerium?</b>

One pill of fibrocerium to heal one permanent injury or chronic condition ailment in 15 to 30 days.
Fibrocerium will also provide partial and lesser enhancing effects of luciferium while it's active in the body:
* Improved consciousness (+5%)
* Reduced pain (×90%)

<b>Fibrocerium always causes an addiction</b>. But it doesn't built-up tolerance and cannot cause an overdose.
With the addiction comes the need to take fibrocerium. By default, the "Social drugs" drug policy will automatically order the colonist to take one pill of fibrocerium, if it's possible, below the 10% need mark, which is after 27 days of the previous take.
It takes 45 days to overcome the addiction. If a pawn takes another pill of fibrocerium while under the addiction, it will progress by 33% (on the UI the addiction stops at 100%, so it will regress by 33% there).

When a pawn stops taking pills of fibrocerium, and the need comes to 0%, then the withdrawal phase will start. Below is the list of withdrawal symptoms:
* Impaired consciousness (90% max)
* Serious pain (+15%, normally comes with −10 mood penalty)
* Increased Social Fight Chance (+200%)
<b>The withdrawal phase will end after 15 days</b> but can last longer if several fibrocerium pills were taken in a short time.

<b>About the mod development</b>

Safe to install or remove with an ongoing save.
Should be compatible with everything.]]>
  </description>
  <modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True"></modIconPath>
  <modDependencies></modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>